翻译+校对 - 遗落星痕 Ice北极熊
时间轴 - Ice北极熊 视频 - Joc
So let's build our first app Scott do you trust me?
让我们构建我们的第一个程序， Scott 你信任我吗
I do trust you.
当然了
All right so I've installed the .Net Core SDK, I just downloaded this and I went through the installer.
那么我已经安装了 .NET Core SDK ，我只需要下载它，还有我已经安装好了程序
So you've done this so
你也应完成了这些步骤
it's one of these things, we did it in the past.
我们在过去也做过这些
But how do I know it worked?
但我怎么知道它是否起作用呢
Okay, so go over on to your command line.
好的，打开你的命令行
And type dotnet --version.
输入 dotnet --version
You already did it.
哦，你已经完成了
Well I just typed dotnet by itself.
我刚才直接输入了 dotnet
So it actually shows that it exists.
这说明 dotnet 已经生效了
Otherwise you would have got some error.
否则是会报错的
That's a good point.
这是一个很好的开始
And actually I can type where dotnet,
事实上我可以输入 where dotnet
and it'll tell me not only that it exists, where it is.
它不光会告诉我 dotnet 是否存在，还会告诉我它被安装到哪里了
But where it is on the disc.
但是它到底在磁盘什么位置
You see it's in program files.
你可以在 Program Files 中找到它
So let's make sure that you're using the right version.
让我们来确认一下你使用了正确的版本
So we're on 2.0.
我们需要 2.0 的版本
So dotnet --version.
输入 dotnet --version
Okay. And I got 2.0.2.
然后，我们会得到 2.0.2
You'll get 2.0.something.
你会得到 2.0.X 的版本
And this is a patch version.
这是一个补丁版本
It's like a like some minor changes have happened
就像是在新版本中发生的一些小的变化
Mm-hm. But 2.0 is what matters
嗯嗯 但 2.0 这部分是不会变的
so I've done that, what else can I do?
我们已经完成了这些，接下来呢？
So let's, some people are comfortable, let's do a dotnet --help
让我们来试下 dotnet --help
because it's always good for people to know that
这个指令对解答大家的疑问
there's a place where they can go and see what's happening
是很有帮助的
So if you type dotnet --help, let's just see what happens
所以如果你输入 dotnet --help ，让我们看看会发生什么
Right, so I can type dotnet --help, and
好的，我输入了 dotnet --help
any of these commands have help
所有的这些命令都是帮助提示
There's help through the whole time
通过整个过程的帮助
Everything
每件事
So it tells you, if you want to do something new, restore packages, run them.
当你想新建项目，还原依赖包，或运行项目时，它能告诉你该怎么做
This is a good rundown of everything you need to know
在你使用 dotnet 命令时碰到的任何问题
that you can use with a dotnet command
都可以在这里找到答案
Now a lot of this might not be familiar
现在有一些部分可能还不够完善
Some of it might be confusing.
其中一些可能会让人困惑
But we're gonna focus kind of on basics
但我们要需关注基础用法就够了
and I think that making stuff and running stuff and
而且我觉得我们开始的时候只需用到
building stuff is probably where we'll start for this.
编辑、运行或者编译
That's where we would be right now.
这就是我们目前要做的
For this module.
这个模块里
That's where we'll be right now.
这就是我们目前要做的
Okay. One of the cool things
好吧一个很酷的东西
especially with dotnet 2.0 is the number of the templates that
尤其是现在 dotnet 2.0 在命令行中
have come out of the box in the command line.
有着数量可观的模板
Okay, what is a template?
好的，模板是什么
So a template is, I think of it as a starting ground.
模板，我认为它就像一个初始的环境
Something that gives you a form or structure
给你一定的格式或结构
that helps you write your code eventually.
最终用来帮助你编写代码
So for those of you who are out there and
所以，这有点像类似于
you've used PowerPoint and PowerPoint
你使用 PowerPoint 幻灯片
has different templates that gives you styles and guidelines.
有不同的模板，模板有不同的风格和向导
Think about this as your PowerPoint for your code.
就把它当作你代码的 PowerPoint
Okay, so I've got, console apps, and web apps, and
好的，所以我们有控制台应用程序，和 Web 应用程序
test apps, and all different flavors.
测试应用，等很多不同的类型
Different kinds of actions we will actually have a look at.
对各种不同的类型，我们都会尝试一下
So should we go and see what kind of apps they give us?
那我们应该去看看 dotnet 能带给我们什么样的程序
All right, let's do it
好的，让我们看看
So let's have a look at dotnet new
让我们看看 dotnet new
That's what I always type
这是我们经常会用到的类型
dotnet new, all right, I get a nice table
dotnet new ，好的，我得到一个看起来很赞的列表
And actually some stuff scroll by
事实上，这还可以滚动
So these are options for dotnet new and it's worth pointing out
这些是 dotnet new 的选项
that we've got help again which is actually help for new and
注意，我们再次看到 help ，而这与刚才的 help 不同
this is little interesting thing to point out very briefly,
这是一个很有趣的事情，简单地说
when I type dotnet --help, I get top level help.
当我键入 dotnet --help 时，我会得到最顶层的帮助信息
When I type dotnet new --help I get help for new.
当我输入 dotnet new --help 时，我会得到关于 new 命令的帮助信息
That is actually not the first time
这真是我第一次知道
I've done this all the time but I've never noticed that.
我一直以来都使用这个命令，但从来没有注意过这些
Isn't that great?
那不是很好吗
Well, what's also interest is if I type dotnet new something
哇，有趣的是如果我输入 dotnet new
I can get the help for that template.
我能得到的帮助模板
Could you run that, and we could see?
你能运行嘛，我们可以看一下
So this is the console application template
这是一个控制台应用程序模板
And here's help options specifically for the console
这是专门为控制台提供帮助的选项
And why this is useful is
为什么这个选项非常有用呢
let's say that I go and get a third party template
假设我使用一个第三方的模板
I get a template from somewhere else.
是我从其他地方得到的
That template might have a lot complicated options and switches of its own
而这个模板本身就有复杂的选项和选择
So dotnet --help is top level.
那么 dotnet --help 是顶层的帮助指令
dotnet new --help is help for new.
dotnet new --help 是 new 命令的帮助指令
And then if I put --help for a specific template name
然后如果我在特定的模板名后再加上 --help
I'm gonna get a help for that.
那我会得到关于此模板的帮助信息
It's pretty cool.
这很酷呢
That is pretty cool.
这是很酷
I have literary found that out during this recording.
我发现这跟文学记录很相似呢
I'm gonna learn from you and you're gonna learn from me.
我要向你学习，你也向我学习
See and We're gonna have a great time.
我们会有一段美好的时光
So I just went back to what you told me dotnet new.
所以回到你告诉我的 dotnet new
I see a list of templates, I see a list of short names.
我看到一个模板列表，和对应的缩写
Names, and you also see a different languages as well that are supported
这里包括了模板名，还有所支持语言的不同
Mm-hm, and in this case, C# is in brackets
嗯嗯，比如说这里， C# 就在支持的语言中
that's indicating that it is the default
而且是被钦定为默认选项
But we can also do F#, which is a great functional language
但我们也可以使用 F# ，这是一个优雅的函数式编程语言
or VB, which is a good language for beginners to try out, okay?
或者 VB ，这种语言对初学者尝试会更友好，对吧？
All right so, lets make one, you wanna make a folder then?
好，让我们创建一个，你想创建一个文件夹吗？
Yeah, yes, so lets make a folder
嗯，可以啊，我们先创建一个文件夹
Myconsoleapp
名为 Myconsoleapp
All right.
好的
So I have an empty folder here
我这里有一个空的文件夹
Exactly
确切地说
And cuz we're gonna build a contact, dotnet new console
因为我们要建立一个联系， dotnet new console
dotnet new console
And a console app is one that just kinda in text mode here
控制台应用就是我们这边所使用的类型
Exactly
没错
So let's have a look at what happen when you type
当输入完，让我们看看会发生什么
dotnet new console over there.
dotnet new console 完成
So it says the template was created.
模板已经创建成功了
Successfully.
很好
And then it ran dotnet restore for me
然后运行了 dotnet restore
So in the past, after I typed dotnet new I used to have to say restore.
在此之前，当我输完 dotnet new 我还必须再还原一次
What is it restoring?
需要还原什么
So, it's restoring some of the packages which we'll have a look at.
需要还原一些包，让我们来看一下吧
What comes in there.
这里面是什么
And the packages are those libraries, those dependencies, the things that it needs.
在这些包中包括了对应的库，依赖项，已经它所需的东西
To actually be a console app.
来构成一个控制台应用程序
And then it generated a file, and told me that it took a certain numbers of millisecond.
然后生成了一个文件，还告诉了我执行了多少毫秒
So we got a Program.cs, and we got a csproj, or C# project.
我们有一个 Program.cs 文件，还有一个 csproj ，或者叫做 C# 项目文件
And the C# project is that's where all our packages are?
C# 项目文件里面有我们需要的包
That's where our references to those packages are
这些就是我们引用包
so let's go and just look at that.
所以让我们来看看
I'm just gonna say Type.
我们只需输入 type
Okay.
好的
And output that cuz this is a very small file.
这就是输出，因为这只是个很小的文件
It's really small.
真挺小的
It says that it's using the .NET SDK,
它显示该项目使用了 .NET SDK
the software development kit
软件开发工具包
It's an executable and it's a .NET Core 2.0 app
这是一个可执行的 .NET Core 2.0 应用
and it doesn't have any dependencies beyond the basics.
而且它除了基础库之外没有别的依赖项
It does have some dependencies for outputting to the console, and things like that.
它是有一些类似用于向控制台输出的依赖项
But for the most part, it includes the SDK
但是大多数情况下，它已经包含在 SDK 之中了
and we have no additional references
我们不需要额外的引用
Okay. Okay.
好的 那很好
So, how do I do something with this
所以，接下来我们该怎么做
like what does it actually do let's see it with the code?
我们能够看到他的代码吗
Here's the code, Hello World.
这就是代码， Hello World
Pretty straight forward.
很直接
So do a quick run.
运行一下试试
Is that okay? Yeah, that sounds good.
这样好吗? 可以，听起来不错
Alright, now there's a moment here.
好的，现在在这里需要一点时间
One one thousand, two one thousand, three.
一秒，两秒，三
Do you know what I was doing?
你知道我在干了什么吗
Why did it take 3 seconds to say 'hello world'?
为什么需要3秒才出现 hello world ？
This is the first time you're running the application.
因为这是第一次你运行应用程序
It's got to build it. Yes
需要时间去编译 是的
I've been doing this at the command line
我再命令行这样做
We don't want to spend a lot of time with the command line
我们不想花很多时间在命令行上
No.
好的
So shall we look at it at code?
我们再来看下代码
So we'll use Visual Studio Code.
我们将使用 Visual Studio Code
It's worth pointing out if I zoom in down here
值得说明的是如果我把下面放大
that I've got both Visual Studio 2017 which is a Windows IDE
可以看到我有一个 Windows 下的 IDE ， Visual Studio 2017
And I've got Visual Studio Code which is across platform IDE
以及新的跨平台 IDE ， Visual Studio Code
If you're on a Mac it's a text editor, it's a code editor
如果你在 Mac 上，它是一个文本编辑器，也是一个代码编辑器
Yeah. It's a little bit less stuff
是啊 它包含的东西虽然少一些
but it's very light weight and
但很轻量
it's crossed platforms so we use that.
还可以跨平台，因此我们将使用它作为编辑器
Now I'm gonna type code ., and dot is the current folder.
现在我要输入 code . 在文件夹的路径下
And, it's actually built in now, right, correct?
它会在这编译，对的
Yeah, I'll show you actually.
是啊，我现在将向你展示
We'll go ahead and run that
我们将继续运行
And then there's a command inside of Visual Studio Code
然后在 Visual Studio Code 中调用命令
that adds it to the path.
将其添加到路径
So it's something that you wanna do after you've run code the first time.
所以这是你第一次运行代码后将要做的事情
So we'll go ahead and run that.
我们会继续运行
Okay, Visual Studio Code opens that up, and then this is
好的， Visual Studio Code 打开了，接下来
interesting Visual Studio code pops up a warning here
有趣的是 Visual Studio Code 会弹出一个警告
hey, stuff I need to build this is missing,
嘿，我需要获取一些没有的东西
do you want me to add them?
你想让我获取他们吗
And then it's got a yes and no over here.
然后它有 yes 和 no 的选项
So watch on the left side here where it says bin and obj.
看一下左边这一列，出现了 bin 和 obj 文件夹
I'm gonna hit yes, but you're gonna watch here on the left.
我会点击 yes ，但是你要看着左边列
There it is.
在这里
See?
看到了吗
So, this is just some stuff that .vscode created for itself.
这些东西，比如 .vscode 是 Visual Studio Code 为自己创建的
It's not about C#, just about .vscode.
这不是关于 C# ，只是对于 .vscode
In order to be able to launch this app,
为了能够启动这个程序
these are just configuration files
这些只是配置文件
So you don't need to worry about those
所以你不需要担心这些
But that is something that you want to say yes
但关于这些你只需选 yes 就可以了
So if someone's doing this for the first time, say yes, but don't touch?
如果有人这样做了在第一次的时候，问你 yse 的时候，如果没有选
Don't touch, don't worry about it.
不要选?别担心
Nothing you need to do in there.
你需要做的
And then you had mentioned about the path.
你要记得你的项目路径
If you hit Ctrl+P.
如果你摁 Ctrl+P
I think it's Cmd+P or fancy macintosh button p
我觉得如果用的 Mac 可能是需要摁 Cmd+P
It is Cmd+P
就是 Cmd+P
Cmd+P, is that what it's called?
Cmd+P ，确实是这个吗
Cmd+P, is that what it's called? Yeah.
Cmd+P ，确实是这个吗? 是的
There's a bunch of actions, so that brings up this palette.
有很多快捷键，能够唤出这个提示盘
I just think P for pallet, and
我只是记得P可以唤出来
then if you say what is this here?
然后，该怎么说呢
The greater than symbol
这是一个非常好的标志
Yeah. I think it's called
是啊我觉得要输入
is it add path?
是 add path 吗
Where is it?
在哪里
There's a bunch of commands in here and
在这里有很多命令
one of them adds code to the path
其中一个可以将代码添加到路径
Maybe it's happening automatically now, but I did that once
现在也许是自动发生的，但让我再试一下
You can see also here that there's other options like your
在这里你也可以看到其他喜欢你的选择
color theme and the default shell and things like that
颜色主题和默认的 shell 之类的东西
Yeah, and the VS code website has really good documentation
是啊， VS Code 网站有很多好的文档
about all the little bitty internals that are happening
关于在编辑器中的很多
on the editor
细碎的内容说明
Yeah, it's incredibly easy to edit, to modify
是啊，会让它非常容易编辑、修改
to change the colors, the behavior
改变颜色，行为
So yeah, feel free to explore
所以，随意探索
That's beyond the scope of what we're gonna do.
这就超出了我们要讲的范围了
I'm just gonna double-click, though, on Program.cs,
不过，我要双击 Program.cs
and I'll zoom in a little bit
我要放大一点
And we've got our application right here.
我们还有我们的应用程序在这呢
And I think it's always good for
我觉得大家可能对
people to play around with the Console.WriteLine.
Console.WriteLine 很熟悉
Put your name in it.
把你的名字写上
Run it again
再运行一下
Remove the semicolon and see what kind of errors you get
先删除分号，看看到你得到什么样的错误
It's a really good way to get comfortable with the language
这真是一个熟悉语言的好方法
Now I can make a change, hit Ctrl+S
现在我可以做出改变，按下 Ctrl+S
I could Alt+Tab back over to here, type dotnet run again
我可以 Alt+Tab 切回到这里来，再次输入 dotnet run
It will build, there's that pause
它将编译，停了下来
Then it runs, says Hello Scott
然后它运行，显示 "Hello Scott"
Then I could Alt+Tab back over here, but
然后我可以 Alt+Tab 回来这里，但是
that can get a little tedious.
可能大家都知道了
Yeah, so is there something in Visual Studio Code that
是啊，所以在 Visual Studio Code 里可以
people can use now?
直接执行运行吗
Remember when I was over here,
请记住我在这里的时候
one of the options was Terminal: Select Default Shell.
其中一个选项是终端:选择默认的 Shell
Yeah
是的
I can hit Ctrl and I think it's called the tilde
摁着 Ctrl ，我觉得这叫做波浪号吧
Yeah, you mean the squiggly thing?
啊，你是说弯弯曲曲的东西
The squiggly thing. Yeah, it's a tilde
就是你说的这个 是啊，这是一个波浪号
I always called it
我总是叫它
the squiggly thing until I saw it in a documentation
弯弯曲曲地的东西，直到我在一个文档看到它
I think our Spanish friends would not call it that
我认为我们的西班牙朋友不会这么称呼它
But yes-
但，还真是
The character that goes over
性格太直爽了
the top of the enye.
在顶部
Yeah. So, you hit Ctrl+~ and
好的吧，那么，按下 Ctrl+~
you can, of course Select your shell.
当然你可以 选择您的 shell
Select that your own way, you can pick your own shell.
选择你自己的方式，你可以选择你自己的 shell
I am using PowerShell in this case.
在这种情况下我用 PowerShell
Now I'm actually in a little command line prompt within Visual Studio Code itself.
实际上，现在我在 Visual Studio Code 自带的命令行窗口中
So now, rather than having to go and say, Alt+Tab, and
所以现在，不必再去 Alt+Tab
then do that, I can do it all from here, okay?
这样做，我能做的一切都从这里开始，是吗
So there's my Hello Scott right there, okay?
所以让我们 "Hello Scott" ，好吗
That's one way to do it,
这是一种操作的方法
but still I'd like to do some interactive debugging
但是我想做一些交互式的调试
I'd like to do something a little bit more sophisticated
来做一些更复杂的
than that, wouldn't I?
那么， 我们能做些什么呢
Yeah.
好的
So I'm just gonna move the mouse over in the left hand
我要移动鼠标到左边
you see this red dot.
你看到这个红点
Yeah, that's a breakpoint.
是，这是一个断点
Yeah, and I click on it and make a break point right here.
是啊，我点击它来中断运行
And then I'm gonna go and click on the little bug.
然后我要去点击 Debug
Well, that's pretty intuitive actually.
很棒，很直观
I think so because there's going to be bugs,
我觉得可能会有错误
I know that for a fact.
我认为一定有
Now this text right here,
在这个文本框这
this .NET Core launch,
选择 .NET Core launch
the way that it knows to do that is because I said yes earlier.
它知道我们要干什么，因为我们已经配置了
To the launch.
选择 launch
If I didn't say yes, I would not be able to do the debugging.
如果我不答应，我将无法进行调试
Okay, and Visual Studio Code can do other languages as well
好， Visual Studio Code 可以使用其他语言
like Node and Python and things like that.
像 Node 和 Python 之类
So that file will be different depending on what
文件的不同这取决于
language you're using.
你使用的语言
All right, so I'll hit Start Debugging.
好的，我会开始调试
And then it's gonna go and build it.
然后它会去编译它
And it's thinking, and it's thinking, and there you go.
稍等片刻，然后他就在运行啦
So now we have stopped the application
现在我们的应用程序在显示
before we said Hello World.
Hello World 之前就会停掉
It's just sitting right here, and
程序会直接停在这里
I can hover over different variables.
我可以看到不同的变量
I can see if there's any local variables.
我可以看到如果有任何局部变量
Actually, we can do this real quick.
我们就可以很方便的查看
Let's hit Stop.
让我们停一下
We'll say var i = "Maria"; var j = 9;
让我们写上 var i = "Maria"; var j = 9;
Hit Debug again.
再次点击调试
See?
看到了吗
Yeah.
是的
And then we've got debugging, can look at our call stack
我们在调试中可以看到我们的调用堆栈
and it's a whole interactive experience.
这提供了一个完整的互动体验
It's pretty rich.
很丰富
It is pretty rich, okay,
确实是很丰富的
given that it is a cross platform code editor,
考虑到这是一个跨平台的代码编辑器
it's pretty fantastic.
这是非常神奇的
And it's also worth pointing out not just the squigglies
说明一下哈，这不仅能给我们提示
that it's giving us, if we look here.
如果我们看这里
There's some warnings like is it saying, well, you used i but
比如它会提示有一些错误，你使用一个变量
you never did anything with it?
但是你却从没用它作过什么
But also sometimes you can get, what's the word,
但有时这种事也时可以被允许，这个变量的属性
what is this here, what's that called?
这是什么，应该怎么命名
The light bulb.
灯泡提示
So I can go and say, I wanna extract that method or
所以我可以去说，我想获取方法或
remove that variable, right?
删除该变量，对吧
So you can do little refactorings.
所以你可以进行一些微小的重构
It's going and saying, well, this is really use for nothing.
它会说，这确实是没有使用
There's no reason for that line to be there.
这条线没有理由存在
And I can click on this and it will fix it.
我可以点击，它会解决它
And in this case, it will fix it by removing you entirely.
在这种情况下，它将通过删除这个变量解决它
Sorry.
抱歉
That sounded rather intentional.
听起来像有意为之
That was not intentional.
那不是故意的
All right
好的
so Visual Studio Code will be what we'll use for a little while and
我们将使用一会儿 Visual Studio Code
then we'll eventually graduate to Visual Studio proper.
然后，我们会适当的结束 Visual Studio 这部分
Yeah. Which has even more features, all right?
是啊，还有更多的特性呢，对吧
So that gives you a sense of, and actually, I'm sorry.
所以给你的感觉上，我很抱歉
We never talked about IntelliSense.
我们还没有谈论智能感知呢
Yes so, let's add a read line, cuz one of the first
是的，让我们添加一个行，因为第一行
things that you do is input and output, right?
你做的是输入和输出，对吧
Uh-huh, so WriteLine is our output.
嗯，所以 WriteLine 是我们的输出
Yeah. I'll start typing Console and
我们只需要打上 Console
you'll notice that it's Some, yeah, Console.
你会发现它能够出现 Console
It's giving me IntelliSense
给我们智能感知
Not only that, it's also for beginners.
不仅如此，它能够帮助初学者
It's great to see, it also shows you what that means.
显示这语句是什么意思
Yeah, you're getting like a little bit of documentation there, that's right.
是啊，这有点看起来像是文档，对吧
It will say Console., see this is nice.
输入 Console. ，看这就很棒
And you said ReadLine, and this is coming out of the docs here
然后输入 ReadLine ，这边就是它的文档
and it will tell you the things that could go wrong.
它会告诉你程序可能出错
ReadLine, reads the next characters from the input stream.
ReadLine ，从输入流中读取下一个字符
Yeah, and notice the squiggly, expected a semicolon, go like that, cool
是的，注意这里的分号
and then I'll do this from the command line over here.
然后我会从命令行这样做
I'll say dotnet run
让 dotnet 跑起来
One second, two seconds, three, and
一秒，两秒，三···
now it's paused right cuz it's waiting for me to read the line.
现在停了下来因为它在等我输入
And it did
确实这样
Okay, so you've got IntelliSense,
好的，所以你有智能感知功能
you've got debugging.
有调试功能
All of that, of course, being driven by this here.
所有的这些，当然，是在这里使用的
And just very briefly,
而且非常简单
cuz it's nice to see some of the internals.
可以看到这些内部的操作是很友好的
When we clicked here, remember that this text here,
当我们点击这里，记住这个文本
.NET Core Launch, comes out of this config file right here.
.NET Core Launch 出现的这个配置文件
Right, the reason I'm showing you that is it's important to
真的，我给你展示这个的原因是很重要的
know that there's no magic
要明白这并不是魔术
We are not hiding anything from you, all right?
我们没有对你隐藏任何东西，对吧
You might not necessarily ever wanna change that,
你未必对这些东西感冒啦
but it's nice to know that the thing that drives
但是明白一些关于这些的事是很好的
the drives the debugger underneath is just a text file.
像这个调试器的运作只是依据一个文本文件
And here it's going to go and run our program.
这里会运行我们的程序
When we say dotnet run, our program is really here,
当我们执行 dotnet run ，我们的程序会在这里准备好
myconsoleapp.dll
And it's gonna go and call that.
它会去调用
And then if we wanna go and
如果我们想要
attach to the debugger, there's also the ability to run the app.
获得调试，还有运行应用程序的能力
And then after the fact, attach to it and
就需要连接到它
then debug it once it's already running.
一旦完成，就可以运行调试
All of that is possible with Visual Studio Code.
这一切在 Visual Studio Code 都是可能的
I think it's also worth showing the audience where
我认为值得向观众展示的地方
to go and read more about what's happening with Visual Studio Code.
就是了解有关 Visual Studio Code 更多的事情
So Visual Studio Code is up at code.visualstudio.com.
Visual Studio Code 可以在 code.visualstudio.com 中访问
And this is a really rich marketplace as well for
这里有一个非常丰富的插件
extensions.
扩展商店
There's lots of stuff.
有很多东西
So you can Visual Studio for C# like we are,
我们可以为 C# 和 Visual Studio
or Python or C++ or Go or a million different things,
或者 Python 或 c++ 或 Go 或不同的语言
and their docs are really lovely.
他们的文档也是很丰富的
There's lots of different things you can learn about.
有很多有趣的东西可以学习
You can change styles, you can change behavior.
你可以改变样式，改变行为
You can integrate it with your source control like Git or VSTS.
你可以把它与你的 Git 或 VSTS 这种源代码控制相互结合
You can create your own extensions as well?
您可以创建您自己的扩展吗
Yep, there's a whole section here,
当然，这里是一个整体部分
exactly, on extension authoring.
没错，可以自己开发拓展插件
I think my favorite extension would have to be
我想我最喜欢的扩展就是
the Slides Extension.
Slides
Have you seen that one?
你见过那个吗
Slides? I like the one with
Slides ? 我喜欢的一个
the funky icons.
时髦的图标
This one here gives you fun
这能给你一个
icons for all of your I think they've moved some of
有趣的图标 我认为他们已经移走了一些
those experiences into actual Visual Studio now.
这些体验现在融入了 Visual Studio
Some of these
这些所有
extensions end up becoming a part of Visual Studio itself.
最终扩展成为一个 Visual Studio 本身的一部分
So what's the one you like, slides?
所以你觉得怎么样， Slides
Yeah, so, you can actually write your PowerPoint slides.
是啊，所以，你可以写下你的 Slides
Where'd it go?
哪里去了
I don't know.
我不知道
Uh-oh.
哦好吧
The one I like is Git Lens, G-I-T-L-E-N-S.
我喜欢的是 Git Lens ， G-I-T-L-E-N-S
So that's weird.
好奇怪呀
Maybe their search isn't working today.
今天的搜索这是不工作了嘛
It's actually Git Lens, with a space in between.
其实 Git Lens 在中间啦
So Git Lens is a great one that lets you have
Git Lens 非常非常好用的
annotations of who changed your code and when.
让你知道什么时候，谁改动了你的代码
Okay. So
好的. 那么
similar to how you can do it in Visual Studio where you can
类似于如何在 Visual Studio 中这样做
actually look at everyone.
在那里你可以真正地观察每个人
Yeah, like blame, if you wanna see whose fault it was.
是的，就像监察一样，如果你想知道是谁的错
So here you can see that it was Eric's fault two days ago, and
所以两天前你可以看到这是 Eric 的错
he made a change from this to this.
他改变了这一些
Yeah, I've seen your name on a couple of those, too.
是啊，我也看到你的名字了
I'm kidding.
我在开玩笑
I have not.
没关系啦
The one I was talking about was reveal.
我刚才说的那个是显示的
Reveal?
显示？
So if anyone sort of revealed JS, it enables you to actually
如果任何人透露 JS ，实际上它让你
have a slide experience in the browser, so.
在浏览器中会有一个 slide 的记录
Yeah, so you've got the ability to edit, markdown,
是啊，所以你有编辑，获取拓展插件
do all kinds of things.
做各种事的能力
Exactly
是的
So really can't recommend VS Code enough.
并不是有理由 必须要用 VS Code
But if you're just getting started like we are today,
但是如果你今天像我们一样刚刚开始
Visual Studio Code is gonna be your best bet for
Visual Studio Code 将是你
your editing and your debugging experience.
编辑和调试体验的最佳选择
And it is.
是的
All right. All right.
好吧 好吧
We'll take a short break and we'll be right back.
我们休息一会儿马上回来